# Himanshu Shinde () Featured

Implementation Analyst seeking roles in Application Development,coding,Unit testing,end to end testing,Unit testing,Requirements Gathering,C,C++,Core Java,Servlet,JSP,Struts,Spring,Spring boot,HTML,CSS,MySQL,Hibernate,Angular is,Ionic framework



Current Designation: Implementation Analyst Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: SunONE Technologies pvt Ltd Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Mumbai, Pune
Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Implementation Analyst, System Analyst, Application Development, coding, Unit testing, end to end testing, Unit

testing, Requirements Gathering, C, C++, Core Java, Servlet, JSP, Struts, Spring, Spring

boot, HTML, CSS, MySQL, Hibernate, Angular js, Ionic framework

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

## **Summary**

2 years of software development experience in SunONE Technologies in Pune, India. Extensive background in full life cycle of software development (Waterfall, Agile) process including requirement gathering, Object Oriented design, coding, testing, debugging and maintenance.

Likely to learn new technologies and can work in different environment efficiently.

# **Work Experience**

**SunONE Technologies pvt Ltd** as Implementation Analyst Nov 2017 to Till Date

SunONE Technologies as Implementation Analyst-IT

Nov 2017 to Nov 2019

Projects Handled: # Project: BookMyOPD

(April 2019 to November 2019 (7 months))
Role: Project Leader with Back End Developer

Work Environment: Windows OS, Java Spring Boot & Hibernate Framework, MySQL

Client: Sahyadri Hospitals, Pune

- Object Oriented Designing, coding and testing of Web Application & Mobile Application using Java Spring Boot and Hibernate platform.
- -Programming using Java, Web Services and SQL Server, Hibernate query (ORM).
- OPD Booking system is a multi-user online application that coordinates with Clinic and Patient showing available OPD with doctor details and allows them to Book OPD on one click.
- Also allows clinic admin to manage OPD for daily, monthly and yearly basis in single process (from dedicated mobile application)

# Project: Spectrum Timesheet System

(December 2018 to March 2019 (4 months))

Role: Full Stack Developer

Work Environment: Windows OS, Apache OfBiz framework (ant version) HTML, XML, Groovy, FTL, Java,

MySQL

Client: Target Publication, Mumbai

Responsibilities:

- Developed Web application and services,
- Performed end to end testing with the web app, Database.
- Programming using HTML, XML, Groovy, FTL, Java, SQL Server.

Description:

- Dedicated web application of Employee Timesheet Management System
- The operations of creating employee profile daily timesheet on hour basis, calculate monthly working hours and Generate Reports.

# Project: BizONE ERP System

(July 2018 to November 2018 (5 months))

Role: Full Stack Developer

Work Environment: Windows OS, Apache OfBiz framework (ant version) HTML, XML, Groovy, FTL, Java,

MySQL

Client: Target Publication, Mumbai

Responsibilities:

- Developed Web application and services, Unit testing.
- Performed end to end testing with the web app, mobile app, database and Emails.
- Programming using HTML, XML, Groovy, FTL, Java, SQL Server.
- Deploying code on Cloud using Putty

Description:

- Dedicated web application of ERP System to perform the operations of creating sales orders, receiving payment from customers, requesting inventory transfer and getting follow-up information

# Project: ePerfumery

(May 2018 to June 2018 (2 months))

Role: Back End Developer

Work Environment: Windows OS, Spring Framework HTML, CSS, Java Script, MySQL.

Client: Aarav, Mumbai Responsibilities:

- Provided BackEnd Support and FrontEnd changes.
- Programming using Java, Web Services and SQL Server, Java Script, HTML, CSS.

Description:

- Dedicated web application for Creating fragrances, maintaining fragrance
- Formulas and Managing different role of Managers

Project: BookOTNow

(November 2017 to April 2018 (6 months))

Role: Back End Developer

Work Environment: Windows OS, Java Spring Boot & Hibernate Framework, MySQL

Client: Sahyadri Hospitals, Pune

Responsibilities:

- Designing, coding and testing of Web Application & Mobile Application using Java Spring Boot and Hibernate platform.
- Programming using Java, Web Services and SQL Server, Hibernate query.
- -Deploying code on Cloud using Putty

Description:

- Operation Theater Booking system is a multi-user online tool that coordinates the functions of OT booking for surgeons, secretary, department secretary etc. (from dedicated mobile application)

#### SunONE Technologies pvt Ltd as Implementation Analyst

Nov 2017 to Nov 2019

Extensive background in full life cycle of software development (Waterfall, Agile) process including requirement gathering, Object Oriented design, coding, testing, debugging and maintenance.

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Pune University in 2016

# IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
C, C++, Core JAVA		2019	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
servlet, JSP, Struts, Spring			
spring boot		2019	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
HTML, CSS			
MySQL, Hibernate			
WINDOWS OS			
AngularJs , Ionic Framework			

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Proficient			
Marathi	Expert			
Japanese	Beginner			

### **Affirmative Action**

Category: OBC - non-creamy Physically Challenged: No

### **Work Authorization**

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time